An introduction to communication
management.
So information needs of our stakeholders
needs to be relevant, timely, via the
correct medium and addressing the proper
audience.
So only relevant information should be
communicated to appropriate stakeholders.
Not all information is communicated to all
stakeholders.
And please note that we spend at least 90%
of our time, communicating, which is why
we live in meetings or we're back typing
up reports.
All right.
So I want to point out a couple things.
We have effective communication.
That's giving the right
information to the right
stakeholders at the right
time via the correct medium.
Whereas efficient communication means
giving only the information needed.
No more, no less.